Hello everyone to a new video. It's a try on haul. I ordered three items at Fashion Nova and we all remember Fashion Nova because our favorite or your favorite cat suit is from Fashion Nova.
And since I like this one so much, I thought I'd order there again and I ordered three pieces, all of them wet look and faux leather.
And yeah, that's basically it. Let's dive right into it. I'm going to change into the first outfit.
Oh I like this one.
So cool, the bodysuit. And the zipper seal.
Okay, they're purely for decorative reasons apparently.
But yeah, it's kind of like wet look, fabric and it's really smooth.
I like the cut of it, although I realize again that my upper body is really long.
Because there's a lot of tension going on here.
But otherwise it's fine.
I like the arms and the overall look.
And I think I'm going to, I don't know, compare it
no, not compare it, combine it with some leggings
to see if it works as a top as well.
I love this look with my paradise pants
and this bodysuit I think it works perfect together. It looks so cool. It
almost looks like catsuit or some superhero outfit. I don't know. I have a
belt pouch whatever and I think I'm going to have a look how this one looks
on top of everything else. Just have to figure out how to attach it. That's
awesome too. I don't know which version I prefer with or without the belt pouch
thingy here. You can tell me which one you prefer in the comments down below.
Oh yeah, I could try and close the zipper. Oh okay, that's it. I think I prefer the zipper open.
with a bit more skin exposed. Yeah, I think this one looks better. Okay, cool. I like it.
And I'm going to keep this in mind, but now I'm going to change into the next outfit.
I think I'll go with the catsuit.
I have to say,
I kind of like the Fashion No More catsuit so far. This one is comfortable as well and really long.
The black and white one was good as well. This is size extra small again and I had no problem
getting into it. It's rather a bit loose. Whereas the bodysuit from before was a size small and it
really tight fit. So if there are any measurements, check the measurements when you're ordering some
clothes. It's somehow crazy how the sizes differ. It looks a bit plain especially compared to the
bodysuit with all the other stuff so I'm going to pimp this one as well.
It's just like with, I don't know, Pimp My Ride. Just add a lot of shiny accessories and unnecessary
stuff and it'll look somehow better that's what I did here with the corset
and the metal accessories yeah looks better than the plain catsuit I think I
also have a bag here for I don't know whatever reason because it looks good so
what do you think still look or is it just like what did you do there I don't
know. All I can say is that the catsuit is still very comfy and I think the corset
that's a really nice touch so I'm happy with the basic outfit I'm not sure about
usually. There's one item left and it's a dress. Oh it's a long sleeve dress even.
fake leather again the fabric is thicker than fabric of the catsuit again
curious I think this is going to be cute
This is really cute.
I thought so, but I still think it's cute.
With the puffy sleeves, cool puffy sleeves by the way.
And it sits really tight.
It's size extra small again, which is the perfect choice I guess.
weird is the seam here which makes a weird shape here from the side. Pointy boobs!
Yeah let's see it as a design feature and feel like we're walking on the red carpet for
receiving some music or acting prize or whatever then this would be totally fine.
I want to up style it a bit as well since I also do this with the other items so let's
choose a belt corset harness thing whatever because I have three options this is a harness
of course my trusty trusty metal belt and a corset waspy and I'm going to show you all three
of them and you have to decide which one you like most and write it in the comments down below
I don't know I think this one is so cool for like every day and a bit more toned down
and I like it because it's all black so perfect for a gothic party
but I think the metal belt is like the more eye-catching one
so yeah I don't know my choice between these two I don't think that the Westby was too good
compared with the others yeah I think this is kind of like my favorite because I'm always
choosing the metal bed so today I'm choosing this one yeah I like it okay I think we've seen
all three of the Fashion Nova pieces and I think the body is my favorite. Yeah. Then this dress and
then the catsuit since I have so many other cool catsuits. The one was rather like boring but this
dress is cute and the bodysuit was really cool with the zippers here so I like that one best.
Okay. Yeah. I don't know. See you at the next video I hope. Please consider subscribing to
my channel. Have a nice day. Bye.